You should also include any relevant comments on what you have implement successfully and/or not included. You
can achieve a maximum of 100 points although you can implement all the options below that total >100.
• [5 Marks] Load a 360 photo allowing it to be viewed through Google VR.
5

• [5 Marks] Allow user to change the 360 photo using the GoogleVR button (Have at least 3 x 360 photos to cycle through)

4 x 360 photos
5


• Allow shape annotations to be drawn on the 360 photo from the previous step.                      ?
o [5 Marks] – Line – user configurable via Unity’s Inspector – start (x1,y1,z1) and end point
(x2,y2,z2), colour (R,G,B), line width (pixels). Using your function, annotate 3 items in each 360
photo using different colours and width.
5

o [5 Marks] – Circle – user configurable via Unity’s Inspector – radius, position, orientation,
colour, line width. Using your function, annotate 3 items in each 360 photo using different
parameters to demonstrate the functionality.
5

o [5 Marks] – Text – user configurable via Unity’s Inspector – adjustable text string, position,
orientation and colour. Using your function, annotate 3 items in each 360 photo using different
text strings to demonstrate the functionality.

using dropdown list is best way i can come up to input string. There is a bug, once you select a letter,
the letter will be recorded, but if you want to type the same letter, you select it again, it won't be recorded, 
because the default function only recorded value change event, so user have to select the last option("type string"), which means nothing.
and then user can select same letter. 
5

o [5 Marks] – Freehand pen tool – allow a user to draw directly onto the 360 photo using an eye
cursor and the google cardboard button.

i spent two days on this feature with hundred lines of code, just can't figure it out. i can change pixel on sphere, 
but how to get the interaction coordinates of eye cursor and sphere is the problem. 
0

o [10] Menu – Incorporate a menu to be operated in VR allowing the user to use all the above tools
in real-time (Line, Circle, Text, Freehand pen tool, setting parameters of each)
i've done everything else, except free hand pen tool
8

o [15] Animation – Support animation of text to highlight features of the 360 photo. Provide 3
separate animation scenes around each 360 photo.
§ The style of animation is your choice. For inspiration some other examples and tools used
to create are shown in the following links:

there are 12 text animations.
15

• [15 Marks] - Attention Grabber – Develop a method to direct the users attention so they look at a feature
in the 360 photo. You can assume there is something of interest the user is not aware of and it is your
job to get their attention to the correct location. You should come up with a method of directing the user
to look at object of interest as quickly as possible. You may choose to use arrows, sounds, lighting,
shading, transparency and any other method you can conceive. More sophisticated methods will attract
higher marks. For example arrows alone will be awarded only a few of the potential marks. Links to
provide inspiration:


This grabber contains sound effects to remind user the position of the feature. 
it's 3d sound, the voice volume will change if player move closer. so user could easily find the location of the feature. 
it also includes light, particle system and animation of color change.
15


• [5] Self Assessment - Provide marks for each deliverable you have completed and comments on the
features you wish to highlight to the assessors. Copy paste this section into a text file called
“Assessment.txt” to be included with your submission.

all the orientations are rotating around (0,0,0) instead of themself, there is no way to figure it out,
i've tried to rotate around Space.self and Space.world, looks like line.Renderer doesn't support that.
because if we want to rotate line.renderer, we have to set lineRenderer.useWorldSpace = false, this cause the wrong orientation. 
5

• [10] Video – develop a video to demonstrate each of the features you have implemented. I suggest
allowing 20seconds of video content to demonstrate each feature you have implemented.

10

• For a HD, complete the following extensions
o [25 Marks] – Enhance the function to support 360 video
§ Allow 360 video to replace the static images   YES
§ Support starting and stopping the video        YES
§ Allow all the above annotations to be used     YES
§ Add a timeline allowing the annotations to be present for only part of the video duration    NO

360 video require wifi to play video, because the video is from google website. you can play local video without wifi,
just change the video URL under 360video GameObject in the Main.scene, select Sphere, change video URL on the Gvr video player Texture Script
20


total: 78    extension: 20


